http://www.pva.com.au/privacy

HomeAbout UsAccountingAudit of CompaniesAudit of Not for ProfitsAudit of SMSFsPreparation of AccountsCompanies Setting Up In AustraliaTrust Account AuditsVirtual OfficeBookkeepingTaxCompany Tax ReturnsTrust Tax ReturnsSuperannuation Tax ReturnsIndividual Tax ReturnsLate Tax ReturnsTax PlanningFringe Benefits TaxSuperannuation Guarantee PaymentsLand TaxPAYGPayroll taxFuel Levy RebateTax Audit InsuranceFAQsSuper & InvestmentSuperannuationSelf Managed Super FundsFinancial and Investment AdviceManaging the Finances of Ageing ParentsInsuranceBusiness InsuranceTradesmans InsurancePublic Liability InsuranceCommercial Property OwnersProfessional Indemnity InsuranceMotor Fleet InsuranceLife InsuranceLandlord InsurancePrestige Home and Content InsurancePersonal Accidents & Sickness InsuranceTravel InsuranceWhy Use A Broker?After Hours Emergency ClaimsTeamNewsSeminarsContact Us(02) 9496 2300
PRIVACY
/
TERMS
/
WEBSITES WITH MOBLE
Our MissionThe Peter Vickers Business Group was founded in 1979 by Peter Vickers â€“ a core strength from day one was accounting. In order to satisfy the needs of our clients we have grown to provide a comprehensive range of financial services. We provide these services to a broad range of clients, across a diverse range of industries and professions, both in Australia and overseas.
Talk With Us
Name * Phone * Email * Enquiry *
SubscribeSUBSCRIBE
Talk With Us
Name * Phone * Email * Enquiry *
SubscribeSUBSCRIBE
Talk With Us
Name * Phone * Email * Enquiry *
SubscribeSUBSCRIBE
Text
HOMEAbout UsOur TeamCareersIn the CommunityPartnersNews & InsightsSeminars and EventsContact Us
Talk With Us
ACCOUNTINGTAXSUPER & INVESTMENTSuperannuationSelf Managed Super FundsFinancial and Investment AdviceManaging the Finances of Ageing ParentsINSURANCE(02) 9496 2300
LET'S TALK
SEARCH
Login
JOIN
MENU
TaxCompany Tax ReturnsTrust Tax ReturnsSuperannuation Tax ReturnsIndividual Tax ReturnsLate Tax Returns
Tax PlanningFringe Benefits TaxSuperannuation Guarantee PaymentsLand TaxPAYG
Payroll TaxFuel Levy RebateTax Audit InsuranceTax Returns in the HawkesburyFAQs
Let's Talk
Name * Email * Post Code Enquiry *
InsuranceBusiness InsuranceTradesmans InsurancePublic Liability InsuranceCommercial Property OwnersProfessional Indemnity Insurance
Motor Fleet InsuranceCyber InsuranceLife InsuranceLandlord InsurancePrestige Home & Contents InsurancePersonal Accidents & Sickness Insurance
Travel InsuranceNSW Small Business ExemptionWhy Use An Insurance Broker?After Hours Emergency ClaimsFAQs Insurance
Quick Quote
Name * Email * Post Code* Enquiry *
AccountingAudit of CompaniesAudit of Not for ProfitsAudit of SMSFsPreparation of Accounts
Companies Setting Up in AustraliaTrust Account AuditsVirtual OfficeBookkeeping
Bookkeeping in Windsor, Richmond and the Hawkesbury
Let's Talk
Name * Email * Post Code Enquiry *
SEARCH
Privacy Our Privacy PolicyPeter Vickers Business Group is committed to protecting your privacy in accordance with the Privacy Act 1998 (Cth) and the Australian Privacy Principles. This Privacy Policy contains important information about the type of personal information we collect, the purposes for which it is used, how it is managed and to whom it is disclosed.  It also deals with how you can complain about a breach of privacy laws, how you can access the personal information we hold and how to have that information corrected.What personal Information we collectIn this policy personal information means information from which an individual is either identified or reasonably identifiable.Clients or Potential ClientsThe personal information we collect and store about you is specific to and required for the particular service that we provide to you.  It comprises your name, address details, date and place of birth, contact details.  This can include, but is not limited to, tax file number, Australian business number, bank account and credit card details, business and financial information and data from previous or current insurance policies.Sensitive Information is a subcategory of personal information which may include information or opinion about an individual.  The sensitive information we collect about you may include information about your health, occupational information, professional associations, lifestyle information that relates to insurance and any criminal convictions you may have.Employees and Potential EmployeesWhen recruiting and employing staff, we collect personal information such as your name, address details, telephone numbers, email address and other information specific to the recruiting/ employment activities. This can include, but is not limited to previous work experience, education, references, tax file number and superannuation details.How we collect personal informationWe collect information from you in various ways.Face to face meetings;Telephone enquiries;When you submit an online query form;When you subscribe to our newsletters and seminars online  We may need to collect personal information from another person or entity such as the Australian Taxation Office, ASIC, your bank, your financial adviser, your employer, your lawyer or other sources as required. We do not collect personal information without your consent.When you provide personal information to us about other individuals, we rely on you to have made them aware that you will or may provide the information to us and the relevant purposes for which we will use this information. You also need to inform them how they can access this information.Website and Client Portal UsersWhen using our website or client portal you may provide us with personal information. We will use all reasonable measures to protect any such information from being used for any other purpose, other than the purpose for which it was intended.As well as the information, you specifically provide above, we may gather statistics on its web site to collect information about the number of visitors coming to the site and their location. No identifying information is collected during this process. We use this information for statistical purposes only.We may also use 'cookies'. Cookies are small files, which are stored on a user's computer. They are designed to hold a modest amount of data about a userâ€™s preferences. This allows the website to deliver a page tailored for a particular user, or the page itself can contain some script, which is aware of the data in the cookie and so is able to carry information from one visit to the website (or related site) to the next. It is possible to have your internet browser refuse cookies, but that may reduce the functionality.Why we collect personal informationThe information collected allows us to:Provide accounting services;Provide insurance, financial and investment advice;Source and facilitate finance;Initiate and maintain your and/or your employeeâ€™s membership of superannuation funds;Arrange and place insurance cover;Assess and underwrite risks;Administer your claims or claims brought against you.MarketingWe distribute to our clients and contacts, general information and newsletters regarding services provided by Peter Vickers Business Group. We may also send you information of new services; events or articles we think will be of interest to you.Direct Marketing Opt OutIf you do not want to receive marketing correspondence from us, you can choose to opt out.  To opt out, you can either:Use the unsubscribe function in our emails;Contact us using the Contact Details belowHow we store personal informationWe will store your personal information in a number of ways:In firewall and password protected electronic record management systemsIn paper files stored in physically secure premisesThe only people who are permitted to access personal information are those employees or contractors who need personal information to do their jobs. All employees and contractors are contractually bound by the confidentially agreements in place on how personal information must be treated.We take all reasonable steps to ensure that all personal information we hold is secure from any unauthorised access, misuse or disclosure, however we cannot guarantee that unauthorised access will not occur.Disclosure and exchange of Information with overseas partiesThe personal information that we collect from you may be disclosed to other parties who are involved with the provision of our products and services to you.Such parties include your insurer, any insurance intermediary involved in the transaction, service providers such as claims assessors, investigators or lawyers (should they be required in the event of a claim) and other insurers (for the purpose of seeking claims recoveries or to assist them to assess insurance risks.Where we have recommended an overseas insurer such as Lloydâ€™s of London we may be required to disclose the information to them. We will tell you at time of advising you on your insurance if they are overseas and in which country the insurer is located.The Back Office Shared Services Pty Ltd (BOSS) team of Peter Vickers and Associates Ltd, located in Bangalore India, may access personal information for the sole purpose of performing accounting services.  BOSS abides by The Australian Privacy Principles.The PVBG directors and team members travel regularly overseas. Conducting work from abroad may require the temporary storage of personal information, accessed from our databases, on the mobile device being used.Access to and accuracy of personal informationIf you wish to access or correct the personal information, we hold about you at any time you can do so by contacting us using the Contact Details noted below.If we are unable to provide you with the requested information, we will provide you with a written explanation.We do not charge for receiving a request for access to personal information or for complying with a correction request.  Where the information requested is not a straightforward issue and will involve a considerable amount of time we may charge a reasonable fee.  In such an instance we will advise you of the fee prior to proceeding with the request. ComplaintsWe are committed to resolving complaints you may have, please contact us at any time by using the Contact Details below.We will consider your complaint through our internal complaints resolution process and we will try to respond with a decision within 20 days of you making the complaint.PVBG Privacy OfficerEmail: services@pva.com.auPeter Vickers Business GroupSuite 2, 345 Pacific HighwayLindfield NSW 2070PH: (02) 9496-2300If we cannot resolve the complaint to your satisfaction within a reasonable time, you or we may refer the complaint to the Office of the Australian Information Commissioner.
Talk With UsManage, protect and grow your wealth with attainable life enhancing advice each and every quarter.
Our Services
Virtual Office Accounting,virtual office We execute on the critical regulatory, legal, accounting and administrat…
Bookkeeping Accounting,bookkeeping Use Peter Vickers Business Group's bookkeeping services,Â we have a gra…
Trust Account Audits Accounting,trust,trust account audit At Peter Vickers Business Group. we provide external examinations of law…
Accounting Accounting,service,accountancy advice Accounting is one of our core strengths at Peter Vickers Business Group.…
Audit of Companies audit,Accounting At Peter Vickers Business Group, we will ensure your company audit is co…
Audit of Not for Profits audit,not-for-profits,Accounting Auditing not-for-profits is one of Peter Vickers Business Group's specia…
Audit of SMSFs SMSF,audit,Accounting Contact our SMSF specialist team at Peter Vickers Business Group, our au…
SERVICESAccountingTaxSuper & InvestmentInsurance
SUBSCRIBEJoin our newsletter subscription
First Name * Your Email *
SYDNEYSuite 2/345 Pacific Highway,Lindfield, NSW 2070T: 61 2 9496 2300services@pva.com.au Peter Vickers Insurance BrokersSuite 2/345 Pacific HighwayLindfield NSW 2070T: 1300 784 011 enquiries@pvib.com.au
WINDSORSuite 3, 31 Brabyn StreetWindsor, NSW 2756T: 61 2 4577 4455 windsoroffice@pva.com.au
Follow us on Social Media
Â© Copyright 2018 VICKERS GROUP Pty Ltd | 1300 784 011 | 02 9496 2300 |  Privacy
Follow us on Social Media
Chartered Accountants Liability Limited by a Scheme under the Professional Standards Legislation - AFSL 229302  |  Peter Vickers Insurance Brokers Pty Ltd AFSL 229302 ACL 229302Peter Vickers Insurance Brokers is part of the Steadfast broker network.
